<tunable name="mozilla_read_generic_user_content" dftval="true">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mozilla to read generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mozilla_read_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mozilla to read all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mozilla_manage_generic_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mozilla to manage generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mozilla_manage_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mozilla to manage all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>

<tunable name="chromium_read_generic_user_content" dftval="true">
<desc>
<p>
Allow chromium to read generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="chromium_read_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow chromium to read all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="chromium_manage_generic_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow chromium to manage generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="chromium_manage_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow chromium to manage all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>

<tunable name="mutt_read_generic_user_content" dftval="true">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mutt to read generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mutt_read_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mutt to read all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mutt_manage_generic_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mutt to manage generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="mutt_manage_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow mutt to manage all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>

<tunable name="thunderbird_read_generic_user_content" dftval="true">
<desc>
<p>
Allow thunderbird to read generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="thunderbird_read_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow thunderbird to read all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="thunderbird_manage_generic_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow thunderbird to manage generic user content (i.e. content that is not specific to an application).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>
<tunable name="thunderbird_manage_all_user_content" dftval="false">
<desc>
<p>
Allow thunderbird to manage all user content (including content that is specific to an application, such as the configuration files of other applications in the users home directory).
</p>
</desc>
</tunable>

